

Aleksandar Krstevski

Date of birth: 15/06/1991

Nationality: Macedonian/citizen of the Republic of North Macedonia

Gender: Male

CONTACT

Bataljon Stiv Naumov 16/17, null7000 Bitola, North Macedonia

aleksandar nk bt@yahoo.co m

(+389) 078381316

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/aleksandar-krstevski-b6a93316a/?fbclid=lwAR261BslRlgpKFAYjvtc7sYLsy23gVdfaCabVV01zIHC3Klr9tk1-ybl9j0

Skype: aleksandar.krstevski1

7

ABOUT ME

An experienced HR officer who strongly believes in rewarding employee environment by letting the employs know that they make a difference and their job is recognized. The other thing I'm passionate the most is the graphic design and 2D digital drawin. It started as a hobby and then it became a passion which evolved with a certificate.... Currently my passion is becoming a purpose and one day I hope it will become a profession.

WORK EXPERIENCE

23/03/2016 - CURRENT - Bitola, North Macedonia

HR Officer

Kromberg & Shubert

Providing support in the various human resources and functions such as:

- 1. recruitment and selection
- 2. training and development
- 3. performance monitoring
- 4. employee counseling
- 5. solving absenteeism problems
- 6. organizing motivational activities

10/06/2014 - 22/03/2016 - Bitola, North Macedonia

Operator

Sport Life

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/10/2011 – 09/09/2014 – Makedonska Falanga 37, Bitola, North Macedonia

Bachelor Of Informatics

"St. Kliment Ohridski" University, Bitola Faculty of Technical Sciences

01/10/2015 – 30/09/2016 – Vasko Karangelevski, Bitola, North Macedonia

Pedagogical Qualifications

"St. Kliment Ohridski" University, Bitola Faculty of Education

01/09/2019 - 30/12/2019 - Bitola

Autodesk 3DS Max

Kumev brothers production

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Macedonian

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

English

Listening C1	Reading B2	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	Writing B1
		R2	R2	

DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office / Microsoft Excel / Microsoft Word / Microsoft Powerpoint / Outlook / Skype / Google Drive / LinkedIn / Instagram / Social Media / Facebook / Internet user / Good listener and communicator / Team-work oriented / Motivated / Decision-making / Gmail / Creativity / Responsibility / Conflict resolution / Analytical skills / Reliability / Flexibility / Good time management / positive thinking / Problem-solving / Ability to Work Under Pressure / 3D Max

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: B

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Graphic designing

Graphic designers create visual concepts, using computer software (3ds Max, Photoshop) or by hand. Develop the overall layout and production design for various applications such as advertisements, brochures, magazines, and corporate reports.

Painting

Workout

Watching movies

Traveling